Volunteering is a significant life experience for any high school student studying in BC, Canada
봉사활동은 캐나다 BC주에서 공부하는 모든 학생에게 있어 삶의 중요한 경험입니다
It is not only a part of the graduation requirement,
이는 졸업 요건을 충족시키기는 것 이상으로
but it's also an opportunity for your child to develop characteristics such as:
본인과 타인을 이해하기 위한 동정심, 인내, 동기 부여 등
compassion, resiliency and self motivation  to gain understanding of oneself and others
학생의 인성 개발에 도움이 될 수 있고
to build new friendships and network with the local community
지역 사회 내 새로운 우정과 네트워크를 쌓아서
and also to create a sense of belonging in their new environment.
새로운 환경 속 소속감을 만들어 주는 기회이기도 합니다.
At Bodwell High School we understand the importance of this area of life learning
보드웰에서는 이와 같은 삶의 학습을 중요시 하되
and the challenges our students may encounter given that they have no direct connections here.
학생이 직접적인 연계가 없는 상태에서 겪을 어려움을 알고 있습니다
Therefore an extensive support system and programs have been developed
그렇기 때문에 주중과 주말동안 학생이 참여할 수 있는
for students to sign up and participate during weekdays and weekends.
다양한 지원 시스템과 프로그램이 만들어져 있습니다.
There are individual and group volunteering opportunities that are available for all students to sign up
모든 학생은 개별 및 그룹 봉사활동에 참여 가능하고
and are mentored by school staff
이는 학교 스텝에 의해서 멘토링됩니다
Students interested in campus jobs and school activities are individually recruited
교내 봉사활동 및 학교 액티비티에 관심있는 학생은
and selected through a brief interview process.
간단한 인터뷰를 통해 개별적으로 선발됩니다
As for the group volunteer opportunities,
단체 봉사활동 기회로는
there are many chances for students to join  local festivals
학생이 지역 행사에 참여해서
to volunteer and help out and to learn their cultures; like this one.
이처럼 봉사하고 문화 또한 배울 수 있습니다
For off-campus community volunteer opportunities,
학교 밖 지역 봉사활동 기회로는
the newly designed signup systems allow students to sign up online in their own time
학생이 학생 포털 계정에 접속해서
by accessing their student portal account.
개인 시간동안 온라인으로 신청할 수 있도록 되어 있습니다
We have also incorporated volunteer opportunities into our Saturday E and after-school clubs.
또한 토요 심화학습 및 방과후 클럽 활동 시간에 봉사활동 기회가 주어지기도 합니다
By checking in with the parent portal my child website and student portal
부모님과 학생 모두 부모님 포털과 학생 포털에 접속해서
both parents and students are able to monitor what students have accomplished during their stay in Bodwell.
학생이 보드웰에서 달성한 일들을 확인할 수 있습니다
They are able to track a student's experience, not only academically,
포털에서는 학생의 학업 뿐만아니라
but also maintain a record of participation in students life skill building activities.
학생 생활 스킬 개발을 위한 액티비티 기록도 확인할 수 있습니다
Student life experience and volunteer work are important for post-secondary application and beyond
학생의 삶의 경험과 봉사활동은 대학 진학 및 그 이후에도 중요합니다
It helps your child explore their own sense of self and life direction
이는 학생이 자아를 성찰하고 삶의 방향을 찾는 데 도움을 줍니다
At Bodwell, we hope to promote thoughtfulness and provide a meaningful experience through volunteer work.
보드웰에서는 봉사활동을 통해 학생이 성숙해지고 의미있는 시간을 갖도록 하고 있습니다.